<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="terms_and_condition"><b>TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE</b>\n\n<b>1. ACCEPTANCE</b>\n1.1 Use of this “I Just Called To Say....” Application constitutes acceptance of these terms and conditions, which constitutes a binding agreement between you (“You”) as the user and Jimmy’s Business Solutions CC (“Jimmy’s”) and shall govern all use of this Application.\n\n1.2 If You do not agree to these terms and conditions, You should an uninstall or delete this Application immediately.\n\n<b>2. DEFINITIONS</b>\n2.1 “Affiliate” means any person, firm or corporation which is an affiliate or associated entity of Jimmy’s Business Solutions CC, as designated by Jimmy’s from time to time.\n\n2.2 “Jimmy’s” shall mean Jimmy’s Business Solutions CC.\n\n2.3 “Application” shall mean this “I Just Called To Say....” mobile device application.\n\n2.4 “Policies” means the various Jimmy’s policies, which form part of this Agreement and which will be updated from time to time.\n\n2.5 “CPA” shall mean the Consumer Protection Act no. 68 of 2008.\n\n2.6 “Contacts” shall mean the contacts or directory of address details and telephone numbers in your mobile device.\n\n2.7 “You” or “Your” means you as the user of the Application.\n\n2.8 “Intellectual Property” means all intellectual property relating to the Application including patents, designs, copyright, trade marks, know how and trade secrets.\n\n<b>3. AGE</b>\nYou may only use this Application if you are eighteen years old or older. If You are younger than eighteen, You are required to get Your parent or guardian to accept these terms and conditions on your behalf.\n\n<b>4. LICENSE</b>\n4.1 Subject to these terms and conditions, Jimmy’s hereby grants to You a personal, non exclusive, non transferrable, limited and revocable license, to use the Application for personal and private use only.\n\n4.2 This license may be terminated immediately by Jimmy’s in the event of any breach by You of the provisions hereof and otherwise on 30 (thirty) days notice.\n\n4.3 These terms and conditions may be updated from time to time by Jimmy’s.  If You do not agree to be bound by the updated terms and conditions, You are requested to immediately uninstall, delete and cease all use of this Application.\n\n<b>5. PAYMENT</b>\n5.1 The payment terms shall be as set out below and in the payment Policy from time to time.\n\n5.2 You shall on commencement of the use of the Application pay to Jimmy’s an initial amount as stated in the Google Play Store.\n\n5.3 In view of Your ongoing use of the Application, Jimmy’s reserves the right to charge additional monthly, annual or periodic amounts for the use of the Application.  If at any stage, You are not happy to pay the ongoing fees, as notified to You, You will be obliged to uninstall or delete the Application and cease all use thereof.\n\n<b>6. PRIVACY</b>\nWith regard to any personal information provided, this will be subject to Jimmy’s privacy Policy and data privacy and data protection laws. The privacy Policy of Jimmy’s will be found at www.......... .com\n\n<b>7. INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY</b>\nAll Intellectual Property including trade marks, copyright, patents, know-how and other intellectual property rights of any nature relating to the Application are owned by Jimmy’s.  Alternatively, Jimmy’s is the authorised licensee of any such Intellectual Property used in this Application and it is authorised to sub license any such Intellectual Property to You.\n\n<b>8. USE</b>\n8.1 Provided and whilst You fully comply with these and conditions, You are hereby granted permission to use this Application, provided that it is only used for Your personal and private purposes.\n\n8.2 You will not duplicate, transfer, give access to, copy or distribute any part of the Application in any medium without the Jimmy’s prior written authorisation.\n\n8.3 You will not attempt to reverse, decompile, alter or modify any part of the Application.\n\n8.4 In order to use this Application, You acknowledge and agree that You will provide Jimmy’s with Your mobile phone number and true name. You expressly acknowledge and agree that in order to facilitate the operation of the Application, the Application may periodically access your contact list or address book on Your mobile device to find and keep track of mobile numbers of other users of the Application.\n\n8.5 When providing Your name and mobile number, You must provide accurate, truthful and complete information. Further, You hereby give Your express consent to Jimmy’s to access Your contact list and address book of mobile numbers, in order to provide and use the Application. Jimmy’s does not collect addresses or email addresses and primarily only mobile numbers.\n\n8.6 The purpose of the Application is to have fun, amuse, entertain and enjoy the Application with your Contacts.  Any use which embarrasses, defames, derides, abuses or in any way causes prejudice to any other person is not authorised and shall be a breach of this Agreement entitling Jimmy’s to immediately terminate Your use of the Application.  Jimmy’s accepts no liability whatsoever for any unauthorised, prejudicial or harmful use of the Application.\n\n8.7 The Applications allows You and other users to submit text, ringtones, photo’s, data and other communications submitted by You to be forwarded to the relevant contact. These submissions or messages may be hosted, shared and/or published to other users or contacts and may be visible to other users of the Application. As a result forwarding any message, status, data or other communication may be broadly published and exposed, which may result in harm or prejudice to others. It is therefore advisable not to submit any communication, data, ringtone and communication, unless You are entirely comfortable that this may be exposed, published or shared.\n\n8.8 You will be solely responsible for Your own submissions and communications and the consequences of posting, communicating or publishing them. The Application is simply a method or medium or application which facilitates the forwarding and communication of such data, communications and images.\n\n8.9 Please do not forward, post or communicate any data or communications in respect of which You do not have the necessary licenses, rights, consent and permission and which may infringe the intellectual property of others.\n\n8.10 You therefore agree that You will not submit any material, data or communications that is copyrighted, protected by trade secrets or otherwise subject to third party intellectual property and proprietary rights, as well as privacy and publicity rights, unless You are the owner of such rights or have permission from the rightful owner to use, forward and communicate such material, data and communications.\n\n8.11 You also agree to not publish any false statements, misrepresentations or prejudicial information and data, submit material that is unlawful, obscene, defamatory, threatening, harassing, hateful, racially or criminally offensive, which may give rise to civil or criminal liability, violate any law, or which is otherwise inappropriate.\n\n8.12 In addition You will not post any advertisements or solicitations of business, impersonate any other person, send or store material containing software viruses, worms, Trojan horses or other harmful computer code, files, scripts, agents or programs or interfere with or disrupt the integrity or performance of the Application or any data therein or in any way attempt to gain unauthorised access to the Application or its related systems and networks.\n\n8.13 Adult content must be identified as such.  Jimmy’s does not in any way endorse or accept liability for or support, such submissions, communications or the forwarding of such data.\n\n8.14 You understand that when using the Application, You may be exposed to or receive a variety of communications, data and photo’s and that Jimmy’s is not responsible for the accuracy, usefulness, safety, damage, harmfulness or other repercussions by the receipt or communication thereof to You.\n\n8.15 You further acknowledge and understand that You may be exposed to communications, data and materials which are inaccurate, offensive, indecent, or objectionable and You hereby waive any legal or other rights or remedies You may have against Jimmy’s in respect thereof and agree to indemnify and hold Jimmy’s, its affiliates and their employees harmless to the fullest extent allowed by law, regarding all matters relating to Your use of the Application.\n\n<b>9. USE REUIREMENTS</b>\n9.1 In order to use the Application, You are required to have a compatible mobile device and certain necessary minimum specifications.  The minimum specifications will include Apple IOS devices running..... and Android OS devices running.......and operating in English.\n\n9.2 The versions of the Application software may be upgraded from time to time to add support for new functions, applications and any related services.\n\n<b>10.	WARRANTY</b>\n10.1	Subject to the CPA, Jimmy’s makes no representations whatsoever and gives no guarantees against any latent or patent defects in respect of the Application and all conditions and warranties whatsoever, whether implied or otherwise, are expressly hereby excluded.\n\n10.2	Subject to the CPA, Jimmy’s shall not incur any liability of whatever nature arising in contract or delict from any injury, loss or damage to any person or property arising from the use of the Application.\n\n10.3	Subject to the CPA, no claim shall lie against Jimmy’s arising out of or in connection with any defects in, unsuitability or interruption of the use of the Application.\n\n10.4	The Application is only suitable for the purpose designed and intended and You will ensure that it is only used in accordance with the purpose designed and intended and only in a manner consistent with the instructions given by Jimmy’s from time to time.\n\n<b>11.	INDEMNITY</b>\nWithout derogating from the generality of any of the provisions hereof, and subject to the CPA, Jimmy’s shall not at any time be liable for any claims of whatsoever nature and howsoever arising for direct or consequential loss or damage which may be sustained by You as a result of the use of the Application by You or any of Your contacts and You hereby indemnify Jimmy’s against all such claims.\n\n<b>12.	PROHIBITIONS OF SET OFF</b>\nSubject to the CPA, You hereby waive any right of set off You might have against Jimmy’s in respect of any amount which may now or in the future be or become owing by Jimmy’s to You.  You agree and acknowledge that You will not be entitled to advance the defence of set off or mutual extension of debts or counter claim in any proceedings which Jimmy’s may bring against You for the enforcement of its rights.\n\n<b>13.	INDULGENCE</b>\nNo indulgence which Jimmy’s may grant to You shall in any way be deemed to affect, prejudice or derogate from the rights of Jimmy’s, nor shall such indulgence constitute a waiver or novation of any of the rights of Jimmy’s, who shall not thereby be precluded from exercising any rights against You, which may have arisen in the past or which may arise in the future.\n\n<b>14.	CONFIDENTIAL INFORMATION</b>\n14.1	You and Jimmy’s agree to keep any confidential information that they receive from one another confidential by using the same high degree of care that they would use to protect their confidential information.  Jimmy’s will not disclose Your confidential information to anyone else, unless You allow Jimmy’s to do so.  You must do the same with the confidential information about Jimmy’s.  Jimmy’s can, however, disclose Your confidential information to Jimmy’s employees and contractors, who need to know and use the information to order to perform their obligations in terms of this Agreement.\n\n14.2	Jimmy’s shall, further abide by its privacy and confidentially policy, set out in the privacy policy.\n\n<b>15.	BREACH</b>\nShould You fail to make any payment to Jimmy’s on the due date thereof or should You be in breach of any of the provisions of these terms and conditions of use and fail to remedy such breach within 7 (seven) days after receiving a written demand that it be remedied, Jimmy’s shall be entitled, without prejudice to any alternative or additional right of action or remedy available to it, to cancel any contract with You, with immediate effect.  It is however to be noted that in the event of a serious breach of this Agreement, in Jimmy’s sole discretion, it shall be entitled to suspend Your use of the Application with immediate effect.\n\n<b>16.	LEGAL COSTS</b>\nIn the event that any legal action is taken or any amount remains outstanding and Jimmy’s instructs attorneys to recover such unpaid costs, You shall be liable for all costs incurred by Jimmy’s.\n\n<b>17.	APPLICABLE LAW</b>\n17.1	All transactions shall be governed in all respects by and shall be construed and interpreted according to the Laws of the Republic of South Africa.\n\n17.2	Subject to the CPA, You also agree and consent in terms of Section 45 of the Magistrates Court Act (the MCA) to the jurisdiction of a Magistrates Court having jurisdiction in respect of You, or the claim in terms of Section 28 of the MCA, in respect of any proceedings or claims or action be instituted against You by Jimmy’s in terms hereof or otherwise, notwithstanding that the amount of such claim may exceed the jurisdiction of such Magistrates Court, provided that Jimmy’s may in its discretion be entitled to bring such proceedings in any other court of competent jurisdiction, You agreeing and submitting Yourself to the jurisdiction of the South Gauteng Division of the High Court of South Africa or any other division of the High Court of South Africa chosen by Jimmy’s, in the event of Jimmy’s exercising its rights in terms hereof.\n\n<b>18.	DOMICILIUM</b>\nYou hereby choose Your domicilium citandi et executandi at the mobile number furnished to Jimmy’s, failing which any of Your physical addresses.\n\n<b>19.	ASSIGNMENT</b>\nThe terms and conditions of use and any rights and licenses granted hereunder, may not be transferred or assigned by You, but may be assigned by Jimmy’s without restriction.\n\n</string>

</resources>